http://www.mikeutley.org/privacy-policy

Contact Us
Privacy Policy/Terms of Online UseWelcome to the Mike Utley Foundation website!  The Foundation endeavors to respect the privacy of our visitors and supporters.  To this end the Mike Utley Foundation will never sell, lease or rent your confidential information.  This privacy statement explains data collection and use and how we will protect your personal privacy within our Web site. Please take a moment to review the Privacy Policy as well as the Terms of Online Use.Collection of InformationThe privacy policy notifies you of:What personal identifiable information is collected through this site;How such information is used;With whom your information may be shared;What security procedures are in place to protect you;The Mike Utley Foundation does not collect personal information without your knowledge during your visit to our Web site.  However, the Mike Utley Foundation does at times ask that you provide us with personal information while online.  The types of information would correspond directly with the service you have requested.  Examples of this information would include donations, registrations, joining our 1st & 10 member club, grant applications and all other programs offered by the Mike Utley Foundation.  The Mike Utley Foundation does not sell, lease or rent your confidential information.  However, the need to disclose personal information as required by law, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena, search warrant that would be in the course of legal proceedings or in response to a law enforcement agency request, to enforce our Terms of Online Use or to protect the safety and security of our visitors and our site.SecurityAll information provided to the Mike Utley Foundation is transmitted using SSL encryption to protect sensitive data transmissions from your computer to our Web site.  SSL is a proven coding system that allows your browser to automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us.Periodically the Mike Utley Foundation may post a link to other Web sites.  Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another Web site for which the Mike Utley Foundation has no responsibility.  You are subject to the privacy policy of the Web site you have linked to.Information Regarding Online Requests:Account Registration:  When you are making a donation, joining the 1st & 10 Club, purchasing items or requesting a resource we require that you provide us certain information that allows us to complete your transaction.  This information is used to create an account within our Online Resource Center.  These "cookies" are set to expire whenever you exit your current browser session.The Mike Utley Foundation reserves the right at any time to change the privacy policy by posting such changes on our site. Terms of Online Use:We have taken every effort to design our Web site to be useful, informative and easy to navigate.  Please take a few minutes to review our terms of online use.  By using the Mike Utley Foundation web site you have automatically agreed to these terms.  We reserve the right to make any modifications that are deemed necessary at any time.Restrictions on Use of Our Online Materials:All materials contained on the Mike Utley Foundation website are the copyrighted property of the Mike Utley Foundation.  All trademarks, service marks and trade names are properties of the Mike Utley Foundation.  No online material from our Web site may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, except that you may download one copy of the materials on any single computer for your personal and noncommercial home use only.  You may not use the materials in a manner that suggests an association with any of our fundraising, products, services, events or brands.  You may not copy, reproduce, republish, upload, post, transmit or distribute our Online Material in any way or for any other purpose unless you obtain written permission from the Mike Utley Foundation.The Mike Utley Foundation is not responsible for the content or practices of third party sites that may be linked to our site.JurisdictionThe online materials that are available on the Mike Utley Foundation site have been presented to provide information.  If the site is used from locations outside of the United States, you are responsible for compliance with local applicable laws.  The Mike Utley Foundation may modify these Terms of Online Use, and the agreement they create, at any time, simply by updating this posting and without prior notice.
About UsOur MissionFoundation HistoryMike's BiographyFinancialsGrantsMedia ContactSCI & the NewsSCI StatisticsFoundation NewsPress ReleasesVideoGet InvolvedMake a DonationJoin the 1st & 10 ClubMerchandiseContactMike Utley FoundationP.O. Box 458Orondo, WA 98843(800) 294-4683
Back To Top
Mike Utley Foundation, P.O. Box 458, Orondo, WA 98843, USA(800) 294-4683contact@mikeutley.org
© 2016 Mike Utley Foundation, P.O. Box 458, Orondo, Washington 98843. Powered by Firefly
Cart (0)
